The Yale School of Music D.M.A. Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1987
  - Swansbourne, Clive - piano (Box 72)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2062) (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Syer, Jamie Keith - piano (Box 73)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2062) (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1988
  - Ehrlich, Paul - viola (Box 74)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 74, Folder 1-2)
  - Golub, Peter - composition (Box 74)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 74, Folder 1-2)
  - Toth, Gwendolyn - organ (Box 75)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 75, Folder 1-3)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1989
  - Bailen, Eliot - cello (Box 76)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2064) (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Cassette Tape (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Cassette Tape (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Brooks, Jeffrey - composition (Box 76)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2064) (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Scrapbook (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Corbett, Sidney - composition (Box 77)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2064) (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Cassette Tape (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Kandinsky Romance (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Arien IV (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Arien 1983 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Arien II: Cactus Flower (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Milwaukee Ballad No. 1 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Piano Dreams: Movement 1 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Lang, David - composition (Box 78)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2064) (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - MacDonald, John - composition (Box 78)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2064) (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Cassette Tapes (Box 78, Folder 6-12)
    - Compositions (66 items) (Box 77, Folder 10-11)
  - Milnes, David - orchestral conducting (Box 79)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2064) (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Osborne, Robert - voice (Box 79)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2064) (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook (Box 79, Folder 5)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1990
  - Arcus, David - organ (Box 80)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2065) (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Braun, William R. - piano (Box 81)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2065) (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Darsey, Steven F. - choral conducting (Box 82)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2065) (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Cassette Tape (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Video Tape (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Video Tape (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Jaffe, Claudio - cello (Box 83)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2065) (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Lemelin, Stephan - piano (Box 84)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2065) (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Middleton, Jeffrey - piano (Box 84)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2065) (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Sichel, John A. - composition (Box 85)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2065) (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Clarinet Quintet (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Madrigali Suburbani (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Orchestra Variations (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Posters (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Cassette Tape (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Thomas, Steven F. - cello (Box 86)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2065) (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1991
  - Christiansen, David - organ (Box 86)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2066) (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Connell, David H.A. - organ (Box 87)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2066) (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Duo-Piano Arrangement From Elijah (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Cassette Tape (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Crawford, Carol I. - orchestral conducting (Box 87)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2066) (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Scrapbook (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Cassette Tape (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Dickinson, Thomas - piano (Box 88)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2066) (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Entrekin, Durward N. - organ (Box 89)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2066) (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Harris, Carole M. - violin (Box 89)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2066) (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Lindroth, Scott - composition (Box 90)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2066) (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Clash & Glitter For Orchestra (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - A Fire's Bright Song For Orchestra (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Treatise On Tailor's Dummies (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Relations To Rigor (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Stomp (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Moss, Grant Russell - organ (Box 90)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2066) (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Scrapbook (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Woodson, Susan C. - organ (Box 92)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2066) (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Compact Disc (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1992
  - Cichocki, Jerzy K. - choral conducting (Box 93)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2067) (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Cumming, Edward - orchestral conducting (Box 94)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2067) (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Dubberly, Stephen - piano (Box 95)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2067) (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Gier, David Andrew - trombone (Box 96)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2067) (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Hagy, David - orchestral conducting (Box 97)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2067) (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Swisher, James - piano (Box 97)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2067) (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Tucker, Charles C. - cello (Box 98)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2067) (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Van Cleve, Libby - oboe (Box 99)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2067) (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Wells, Alison - cello (Box 100)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2067) (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 100, Folder 2)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1993
  - Hamilton, Barbara - viola (Box 101)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2068) (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Snyder, Patricia - organ (Box 102)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2068) (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Tieszen, Stephan - violin (Box 103)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2068) (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 103, Folder 2)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1994
  - Argondizza, Peter - guitar (Box 104)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2069) (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Beggs, Sally Cherrington - organ (Box 105)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2069) (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Dolan, Marian E. - choral conducting (Box 106)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2069) (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Dubay, Jonathan - violin (Box 107)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2069) (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Josel, Seth - guitar (Box 108)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2069) (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Lee, Genevieve F. - piano (Box 110)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2069) (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Nikiforuk, Peter James - organ (Box 102)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2069) (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Satterlee, Robert - piano (Box 111)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2069) (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Smith, Jeffrey - organ (Box 111)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2069) (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Scrapbook (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Valdivia, Hector Luis - violin (Box 112)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2069) (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Viton, John - oboe (Box 113)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2069) (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 113, Folder 3)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1995
  - Beck, Jeremy - composition (Box 114)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2070) (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - DeCorsey, James - horn (Box 115)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2070) (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Elhai, Robert - Composition (Box 107)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2070) (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Goode, Elizabeth - flute (Box 115)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2070) (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Scrapbook (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Gross, Steven - choral conducting (Box 116)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2070) (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Videotape (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Harsh, Edward D. - composition (Box 117)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2070) (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Accommodating commonplaces (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Aphoristic bagatelles (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Be not the slave of words (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Opulence / languor / apostasy (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Johnson, Craig Hella - choral conducting (Box 118)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2070) (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 177)
  - Olsen, Timothy John - composition (Box 119)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2070) (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Schnurr, Stephen J., Jr. - organ (Box 119)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2070) (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Sohn, Angela In-Kyung - violin (Box 120)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2070) (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Scrapbook (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Ulben, Deniz - Composition (Box 104)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2070) (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 104, Folder 2)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1996
  - Coxe, Stephen - composition (Box 121)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2071) (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Bagatelles for wind trio (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Les Illuminations (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Piano trio (1993) (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - sound cassette (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - sound cassette (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - sound cassette (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Hui, Melissa - composition (Box 118)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2071) (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Kitagawa, Nobuo - oboe (Box 121)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2071) (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Knehans, Douglas - composition (Box 123)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2071) (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Lee, Min Jung - piano (Box 124)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2071) (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Ring, Mark Milton - choral conducting (Box 125)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2071) (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Strauch, Richard C., Jr. - trombone (Box 125)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2071) (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 125, Folder 4)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1997
  - Aldrich, Simon - clarinet (Box 126)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2072) (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Anzolini, Dante - orchestral conducting (Box 126)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2072) (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Cochran, Grant - choral conducting (Box 127)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2072) (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Kemper, Charles - piano (Box 128)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2072) (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Ronning, Svend John - violin (Box 130)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2072) (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Theofanidis, Chris - composition (Box 129)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2072) (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 129, Folder 3)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1998
  - Dybvig, Teresa Lynn, Piano; 1 scrapbook (Box 131)
  - Hulm, Lance Richard, Composition; 2 scrapbooks (Box 132)
  - Ou, Carol I., Cello; 1 scrapbook (Box 132)
  - Park, Clara, Piano; 1 scrapbook (Box 133)
  - Schmidt, Carsten, Piano; 1 scrapbook (Box 134)
  - Vigneau, Kevin, Oboe; 2 scrapbooks (Box 135)
  - Wiebe, Thomas, Cello; 1 scrapbook (Box 135)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1999
  - Askim, Peter Andrew, Double bass; 6 scrapbooks (Box 136–138)
  - Hung, Chung-Kun, Composition; 2 scrapbooks (Box 139)
  - Perla, James C. (Jack), Composition; 3 scrapbooks (Box 140)
  - Princiotti, Anthony, Orchestral conducting; 1 scrapbook (Box 133)
  - Reynolds, Belinda Leah, Composition; 1 scrapbook (Box 139)
  - Trester, Francine Gail, Composition; 1 scrapbook (Box 164)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 2000
  - Aldridge, Robert Livingston, Composition; 1 scrapbook (Box 165)
  - Jacobs, Jan Pieter, Piano; 2 scrapbooks (Box 141)
  - Louise-Turgeon, Anne, Piano; 1 scrapbook (Box 141)
  - Meltzer, Harold Yale, Composition; 1 scrapbook (Box 139)
  - Turgeon, Edward, Piano; 3 scrapbooks (Box 142)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 2001
  - Becker, Daniel, Composition; 1 scrapbook (Box 143)
  - Gatto, Anthony, Composition; 1 scrapbook (Box 139)
  - Kim, Jeeyoung, Composition; 2 scrapbooks (Box 143)
  - Lent, James Douglas, Piano; 2 scrapbooks (Box 144)
  - Rubenstein, Joseph Aaron, Composition; 1 scrapbook (Box 144)
  - So, Ting Cheong, Composition; 3 scrapbooks (Box 145)
  - Vaneman, Kelly, Oboe; 5 scrapbooks (Box 146)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 2002
  - Hurd, Maureen Lynn, Clarinet; 6 scrapbooks (Box 147–148)
  - Vaneman, Christopher Matthew, Flute; 6 scrapbooks (Box 149)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 2003
  - Brockmann, Nicole Marie, Viola; 2 scrapbooks (Box 150)
  - Cienniwa, Paul D., Harpsichord; 3 scrapbooks (Box 151)
  - Grim, Jennifer Marie, Flute; 2 scrapbooks (Box 150)
  - Novgorodsky, Dmitri Pavlovich, Piano; 1 scrapbook (Box 151)
  - Silverman, Adam Benjamin, Composition; 1 scrapbook (Box 150)
  - Sparks, Tram Ngoc, Choral conducting; 1 scrapbook (Box 152)
  - Starcevich, Sasha, Piano; 2 scrapbooks (Box 151)
  - Thomas, Steven Llewellyn, Choral conducting; 3 scrapbooks (Box 152)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 2004
  - Fabrikant, Einat, Piano; 2 scrapbooks; Evaluations (sealed until 2079) (Box 153)
  - Sanchez-Fernandez, Hector Jesus, Piano; 2 scrapbooks (Box 153)
  - Yang, Wei-Yi, Piano; 1 scrapbook (Box 153)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 2005
  - Bowman, Calvin Andrew, Organ; 1 scrapbook; Evaluations (sealed until 2080) (Box 157)
  - Bulmer, Karen Laurel, Tuba; 1 scrapbook; Evaluations (sealed until 2080) (Box 154)
  - Getnick, Pamela Ellen, Choral conducting; 1 scrapbook; Evaluations (sealed until 2080) (Box 155)
  - Kim, Jeanyi Jacklyn, Violin; 1 scrapbook; Evaluations (sealed until 2080) (Box 154)
  - Kolkay, Peter Christopher, Bassoon; 1 scrapbook; Evaluations (sealed until 2080) (Box 154)
  - Leljack, Dorian, Piano; 3 scrapbooks; Evaluations (sealed until 2080) (Box 156)
  - Srikaranonda, Indhuon, Piano; 4 scrapbooks; Evaluations (sealed until 2080) (Box 156)
  - Wells, Bradley Carter, Choral conducting; 2 scrapbooks; Evaluations (sealed until 2080) (Box 155)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 2006
  - Maroney, Marcus Karl, Composition; 1 scrapbook (Box 157)
  - Serebryany, Vadim, Piano; 4 scrapbooks (Box 158)
  - Wiskus, Jessica, Horn; 2 scrapbooks (Box 159)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 2007
  - Buck, Stephen Mulvey, Piano; 2 scrapbooks (Box 158)
  - Feeney, Timothy Patrick, Percussion; 2 scrapbooks (Box 159)
  - Gard, Richard Jay, Choral conducting; 3 scrapbooks (Box 164)
  - Kellogg, Daniel Dixon, Composition; 1 scrapbook (Box 161)
  - Rosenbaum, Rebecca, Choral conducting; 2 scrapbooks (Box 160)
  - Viney, Liam Vincent, Piano; 1 scrapbook (Box 158)
  - Welch, Bradley Hunter, Organ; 2 scrapbooks (Box 168–169)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 2008
  - Farrin, Suzanne Marie, Composition; 1 scrapbook (Box 163)
  - Johnson, Jared Clayton, Organ; 2 scrapbooks (Box 166)
  - Kamm, Charles William, Choral conducting; 2 scrapbooks (Box 161)
  - Mizrahi, Michael David, Piano; 1 scrapbook (Box 162)
  - Murphy, Keith Andrew, Composition; 1 scrapbook (Box 163)
  - Sharlat, Yevgeniy, Composition; 1 scrapbook (Box 163)
  - Weber, Paul Matthew, Organ; 1 scrapbook (Box 157)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 2009
  - Atapine, Dmitri., Cello; 1 scrapbook (Box 162)
  - Burke, Patrick Alan, Composition; 1 scrapbook; Evaluations (sealed until 2084) (Box 163)
  - Colwell, David Aaron, Violin; 1 scrapbook (Box 162)
  - Hoffenberg, Rick, Choral conducting; 1 scrapbook (Box 161)
  - Kwok, Sarita Kit Yee, Violin; 1 scrapbook (Box 162)
  - Orfe, John C., V, Composition; 2 scrapbooks (Box 167)
  - Sliwinski, Adam Gilbert, Percussion; 1 scrapbook (Box 159)
  - Zubieta, Sebastián, Composition; 2 scrapbooks (Box 163)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 2010
  - Harlow, Brian Preston, Organ; 2 scrapbooks (Box 170–171)
  - Moore, Bradley Paul, Piano; 2 scrapbooks (Box 172)
  - Poletaev, Ilya, Piano; 1 scrapbook (Box 172)
  - Rentz, David Joseph, Choral conducting; 3 scrapbooks (Box 173)
  - Vigil, Ryan Howard, Composition; 1 scrapbook + 12 compositions (Box 175–176)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 2011
  - Brandau, Ryan James, Choral conducting; 8 scrapbooks; Evaluations (sealed until 2086) (Box 173)
  - Brennan, Joel Andrew, Trumpet; 2 scrapbooks (Box 174)
  - Dudley, Eric John, Orchestral conducting; 2 scrapbooks (Box 175)
  - McClellan, Robinson O., Composition; 1 scrapbook (Box 175)
  - Teardo, Frederick Thomas, Organ; 1 scrapbook (Box 172)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 2012
  - Barnson, Matthew, Composition; 1 scrapbook; Evaluations (sealed until 2087) (Box 178)
  - Chan, Wen-Yin, Piano; 2 scrapbooks (Box 184)
  - DiOrio, Dominick, Choral conducting; 5 scrapbooks; Evaluations (sealed until 2087) (Box 182)
  - Hodgson, Aaron, Trumpet; 1 scrapbook; Evaluations (sealed until 2087) (Box 183)
  - Suckling, Martin, Composition; 1 scrapbook (Box 178)
  - Wang, Mingzhe, Clarinet; 2 scrapbooks (Box 183)
  - Wong, Lucas, Piano; 1 scrapbook; Evaluations (sealed until 2087) (Box 184)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 2013
  - Anderson, Greg, Piano and Composition; 2 scrapbooks + 3 volumes of music; Evaluations (sealed until 2088) (Box 186)
  - Buide del Real, Fernando, Composition; 1 scrapbook; Evaluations (sealed until 2088) (Box 179)
  - Jancaitis, Holland, Choral Conducting; 1 scrapbook; Evaluations (sealed until 2088) (Box 182)
  - Liu, Jian, Piano; 1 scrapbook; Evaluations (sealed until 2088) (Box 184)
  - Yanagitani, Ryo, Piano; 1 scrapbook; Evaluations (sealed until 2088) (Box 185)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 2014
  - Cerrone, Christopher, Composition; 1 scrapbook + compositions; Evaluations (sealed until 2089) (Box 188)
  - Cooper, Jacob, Composition; 1 scrapbook + compositions; Evaluations (sealed until 2089) (Box 179)
  - DiEugenio, Nicholas, Violin; 1 scrapbook; Evaluations (sealed until 2089) (Box 181)
  - Honstein, Robert, Composition; 1 scrapbook + compositions; Evaluations (sealed until 2089) (Box 179, Box 188)
  - Kaplan, David, Piano; 2 scrapbooks; Evaluations (sealed until 2089) (Box 185)
  - Powis, Simon, Guitar; 1 scrapbook; Evaluations (sealed until 2089) (Box 180)
  - Usiskin, Laura, Cello; 1 scrapbook (Box 181)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 2015
  - Hearne, Ted, Composition; 2 scrapbooks + compositions; Evaluations (sealed until 2090) (Box 187)
  - Thorburn, Colleen Potter, Harp; 3 scrapbooks; Evaluations (sealed until 2090) (Box 180)
  - Wong, Yan Ming Alvin, Cello; 2 scrapbooks (Box 181)